UNITE International Relations Department Publications 6000/027 PUBS
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Worker's/Human Rights, Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: In Your Hands: Community Action Guide for Human Rights Year and Beyond, 1998; Publication (Box 6, Folder 9)
    Notes: Honoring the 50th Anniversary of the Universal Declaration of Human Rights.
- Worker's/Human Rights: Hotline, Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Justice and Peace Newsletter, 1995; Publication (Box 6, Folder 10)
    Author: Rosaline Costa
    Notes: no.85 (1995:June/July)
  - Item 2: Hotline Newsletter, 1995-1997 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.86, 96- 98
  - Item 3: Hotline Bangladesh, 2000-2001 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    Notes: no.115- 117
- AFL-CIO, Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Convention Resolutions: Book One, numbers 1-130., 1995; Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Notes: October 23-26, 1995.
  - Item 2: Convention Executive Council Report, 1997; Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
    Notes: September 22-25, 1997.
  - Item 3: Convention Resolutions and Constitutional Amendments, 1997; Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: Convention Program, 1997; Publication (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Association of Farmworker Opportunity Programs, Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Biennial Report: July 1, 1994 - June 30, 1996, 1998; Publication (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Clean Clothes Campaign, Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Clean Clothes Newsletter, 1998; Publication (Box 7, Folder 3)
    Notes: no.10 (1998:Aug.)
- Congressional Asian Pacific American Caucus Institute, Publication (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: 105th Congressional Directory, Publication (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Free Trade Union Institute, Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: 1995 Annual Report, 1996; Publication (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Freedom House, Publication (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Global Warning: Press Controls Fuel the Asian Debacle, 1998; Publication (Box 7, Folder 6)
    Author: Leonard R. Sussman
- GIDC, Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Annual Report 1995-1996, 1997; Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Annual Report 1996-1997, 1998; Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: GIDC's Fashion Industry Modernization Center: Grand Opening, 1998; Publication (Box 7, Folder 7)
    Notes: April 24, 1998.
- GIDC News, Publication (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: GIDC News, 1995-1999 (Box 7, Folder 8)
    Notes: v.5:no.4; v.6:no.1, 4; v.7:no.1-2, 4; v.8:no.1- v.9:no.3
- Green Flag, Publication (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: National Breakdown: Are Your Paying Too Much for Your Vehicle Rescue?, Publication (Box 7, Folder 9)
- ICFTU: Constitution, Publication (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Constitution and Standing Orders, 1996; Publication (Box 7, Folder 10)
    Notes: Two copies
  - Item 2: Constitution and Standing Orders, 2000; Publication (Box 7, Folder 10)
- ICFTU: 7th World Women's Conference, Publication (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Conclusions and Recommendations of the 7th World Women's Conference of the ICFTU, 1999; Publication (Box 7, Folder 11)
    Notes: May 18-21, 1999.
- ICFTU: 16th World Congress, Publication (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Statements Adopted by the 16th World Congress of the ICFTU, 1996; Publication (Box 7, Folder 12)
- ICFTU: 17th World Conference, Publication (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Globalising Social Justice: Trade Unionism in the 21st Century, Executive Summary, 2000; Publication (Box 7, Folder 13)
    Notes: 17th World Congress, April 3-7, 2000. Three copies
  - Item 2: Globalising Social Justice: Trade Unionism in the 21st Century, 2000; Publication (Box 7, Folder 13)
    Notes: 17th World Congress, April 3-7, 2000.
- ICFTU: Pamphlets, Publication (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Building Workers' Human Rights into the Global Trading System, 1999; Publication (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Item 2: Fighting for Dignity, 1999; Publication (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Item 3: Trade Union World, 2000; Publication (Box 7, Folder 14)
    Notes: Daily Special Edition 17th Congress of the ICFTU
  - Item 4: Afro News, 1999; Publication (Box 7, Folder 14)
    Notes: no.18 (1999:Dec.)
- ILO: Labour and Social Issues Relating to Export Processing Zones, Publication (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Labour and Social Issues Relating to Export Processing Zones, 1998; Publication (Box 8, Folder 1)
- ILO: World Labor Report, Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: World Labour Report: Industrial Relations, Democracy and Social Stability, 1997-98, Publication (Box 8, Folder 2)
- ILO: Reports, Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Program and Budget for 1998-1999: Summary and Analysis, 1997; Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Notes: Prepared for American Constituents of the ILO
  - Item 2: Decent Work, 1999; Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Notes: International Labour Conference, 87th Session.
  - Item 3: The ILO and Global Change, 1990-1997, Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Item 4: Globalization of the Footwear, Textiles and Clothing Industries, 1996; Publication (Box 8, Folder 3)
    Notes: Sectoral Activities Programme
- ILO: Pamphlets, Publication (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: International Labour Organization, Publication (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Making a World of Difference for Working People, Publication (Box 8, Folder 4)
- ITGLWF: 7th World Congress [Folder 1 of 4], Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Programme, 1996; Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Notes: 7th World Congress, 15-19 April, 1996.
  - Item 2: Decisions of Congress, 1996; Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
    Notes: 7th World Congress, 15-19 April, 1996. Three copies.
  - Item 3: Financial Reports, 1992-1994, 1996; Publication (Box 8, Folder 5)
- ITGLWF: 7th World Congress [Folder 2 of 4], Publication (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Country Reports, 1996; Publication (Box 8, Folder 6)
- ITGLWF: 7th World Congress [Folder 3 of 4], Publication (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Motions for Submission to Congress, 1996; Publication (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: Fighting Exploitation, Building Solidarity, Promoting Workers Rights: An Agenda for ITGLWF Action, 1996; Publication (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: 6th World Congress: Summary of Proceedings, 1996; Publication (Box 8, Folder 7)
- ITGLWF: 7th World Congress [Folder 4 of 4], Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Activity Report (1992-1995), 1996; Publication (Box 9, Folder 1)
    Author: Neil Kearney
- ITGLWF: 8th World Congress [Folder 1 of 3], Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Activity Report (1996-1999), 2000; Publication (Box 9, Folder 2)
    Notes: 8th World Congress, 26-30 June, 2000.
- ITGLWF: 8th World Congress [Folder 2 of 3], Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Financial Reports, 1995-1999, 2000; Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: 7th World Congress: Summary of Proceedings, 2000; Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Global Solidarity in a Global Industry: An Agenda for ITGLWF Action, 2000; Publication (Box 9, Folder 3)
- ITGLWF: 8th World Congress [Folder 3 of 3], Publication (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Rules for the ITGLWF: Proposals for Amendments, 2000; Publication (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Item 2: Motions for Submission to Congress, 2000; Publication (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Country Reports, 2000; Publication (Box 9, Folder 4)
- ITGLWF: Newsletter, Publication (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: ITGLWF Newsletter, 1996-1998 (Box 9, Folder 5)
    Notes: no.1 (1996) - no.2 (1998)
- ITGLWF: Workshop for Women Trade, Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Workshop for Women Trade Union Leaders, 1996; Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Working Womens Rights in Workplace, 1996; Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
    Notes: Included in "Workshop for Women Trade Union Leaders"
  - Item 3: Integration of Women into Trades Union Organisations in the Textile, Garment and Leather Industries, 1996; Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Item 4: Status of Homeworkers in the ILO Convention: A SEWA Report, 1996; Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Mulher e Mercado de Trabalho no Brasil, 1996; Publication (Box 9, Folder 6)
- International Trade Secretariats, Publication (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: One World, One Voice, Solidarity, 1996; Publication (Box 9, Folder 7)
    Author: Heinz Bendt
- American Labor in the New Economy - League for Industrial Democracy, Publication (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Democratizing the Global Economy, Publication (Box 9, Folder 8)
    Notes: American Labor in the New Economy: A Day of Dialogue. Briefing Paper I.
  - Item 2: New Prospects for American Workers, Publication (Box 9, Folder 8)
    Notes: American Labor in the New Economy: A Day of Dialogue. Briefing Paper III.
- Public Services International, Publication (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Focus on the Public Services, 2000; Publication (Box 9, Folder 9)
    Notes: v.7:no.4 (2000)
- Stanley Foundation, Publication (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Making Peace With the Future: The United Nations and World Security, 1995; Publication (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Notes: 30th UN of the Next Decade Conference
  - Item 2: US-UN Realtions, 1995; Publication (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Notes: Vantage Conference
  - Item 3: The Role of the United Nations in Eliminating Weapons of Mass Destruction, 1996; Publication (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Notes: 27th United Nations Issues Conference
  - Item 4: Getting Down to Cases: Enforcing Security Council Resolutions, 1998; Publication (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Notes: 33rd United Nations of the Next Decade Conference
  - Item 5: Global Governance: Defining the United Nations' Leadership Role, 1999; Publication (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Notes: 34th United Nations of the Next Decade Conference
  - Item 6: The United Nations and Civil Society: The Role of NGOs, 1999; Publication (Box 9, Folder 10)
    Notes: 30th United Nations Issues Conference
- Trade & Industy Monitor, Publication (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Trade & Industry Monitor, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 1)
    Notes: v.2-4, 6-7
- TWARO News, Publication (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: TWARO News, 1995-2001 (Box 10, Folder 2)
    Notes: no.34-40
- UNITE, Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: A Pattern of Injustice: On-Going Sweatshop Abuses Behind the Brands at May Department Store Company, 1997; Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Item 2: Ergonomic Facts and Action Manual: A Union Guide to the OSHA Ergonomics Standard and Joint Labor-Management Ergonomics Programs, 2001; Publication (Box 10, Folder 3)
    Author: Department of Occupational Safety and Health
- United Nations: A Global Agenda, Publication (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: A Global Agenda: Issues Before the 53rd General Assembly of the United Nations, 1998; Publication (Box 10, Folder 4)
    Author: John Tessitore; Susan Woolfson
    Notes: 1998-1999 Edition
- United Nations: Pamphlets, Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Algeria's Struggle for Democracy, 1997; Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
    Author: Mona Yacoubain
    Notes: Studies Department Occasional Paper Series, no.3
  - Item 2: UNDP, Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Item 3: A Users' Guide to the U.N. Social Summit, 1996; Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Item 4: Council of Organizations News, 1999; Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.3:no.1 (1999:Spring/Summer)
  - Item 5: The InterDependent, 1998; Publication (Box 10, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.24:no.1 (1998:Spring)
- United Nations: UNDP, Publication (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Building A New UNDP: 1994/1995 Annual Report, Publication (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Cooperation South, 1996; Publication (Box 10, Folder 6)
    Notes: Winter 1996.
  - Item 3: Choices: The Human Development Magazine, 1995; Publication (Box 10, Folder 6)
    Notes: August, 1995.
  - Item 4: UNDP News, 1997-1998 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Witness For Peace, Publication (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Sewing Justice: US Solidarity and the Workers' Struggle in Nicaragua's Maquilas, 1997; Publication (Box 10, Folder 7)
    Author: Ann Jones; Chris Pinc; Leia Raphaelidis; Ed Schwartzman
  - Item 2: Newsletter, 1996; Publication (Box 10, Folder 7)
    Notes: v.13:no.1 (1996:Fall)
  - Item 3: Made in Nicaragua: From the Maquila to the Mall, Publication (Box 10, Folder 7)
    Author: Metta Morton;p Leia Raphaelidis
  - Item 4: A People Dammed: The Impact of the World Bank Chixoy Hydroelectric Project in Guatemala, 1995; Publication (Box 10, Folder 7)
    Author: Julie Stewart; Kevin O'Connell; Marian Ciborski; Matthew Pacenza
  - Item 5: A High Price to Pay: Structural Adjustment and Women in Nicaragua, Publication (Box 10, Folder 7)
    Author: Sharon Hostetler; JoAnn Lynen; Leia Raphaelidis
- Force Ouvriere Hebdo, 2001; Publication (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Force Ouvriere Hebdo, 2001; Publication (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Force Ouvriere Hebdo, 2000; Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Force Ouvriere Hebdo, 2000; Publication (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Force Ouvriere Hebdo, 1996-1999 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Force Ouvriere Hebdo, 1996-1999 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Social Labels: Tools for Ethical Trade, Publication (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Social Labels: Tools for Ethical Trade. Final Report., 1998; Publication (Box 11, Folder 4)
    Author: Simon Zadek; Sanjiv Lingayah; Maya Forstater
- United Nations: UNDP - Choices, Publication (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Choices: The Human Development Magazine, 1996; Publication (Box 11, Folder 5)
    Notes: v.5:no.1 (1996)